http://www.foodlifeline.org/privacy-policy/

Agency Portal
Donate
Volunteer
Food Lifeline Privacy Policy and Terms & Conditions of Use
Food Lifeline appreciates your support and engagement. Your willingness to place trust in our organization is important, and we are dedicated to making the most of your generous donation. Food Lifeline is committed to your privacy and not only maintains strict customer privacy policies, but also ensures a safe environment when you make a donation. We are also proud to follow the Better Business Bureau’s Wise Giving Alliance Standards for Charitable Accountability.
Food Lifeline does not share your information. We will not take your personal information and sell, exchange, or rent it to any other organization or individual.
Any personal information you share with Food Lifeline is only handled by those individuals necessary to transact, fulfill, and/or account for donations.
It is up to the discretion of each donor as to whether or not they would like their names printed in Food Lifeline’s published reports.
What Information Does Food Lifeline Collect?
If you choose to make a donation, Food Lifeline asks for pertinent information to complete your transaction and/or inquiry, such as your name, business, address, phone, and email address.
Other information Food Lifeline collects when you visit the web site includes the number of individuals visiting the site and what pages are being viewed.
How Food Lifeline Uses the Information Collected
Food Lifeline may use your phone number to verify information about your gift, to personally thank you for your donation, or to invite you to a special event.
The personal information that Food Lifeline collects from you is used to fulfill your transaction and/or inquiry. This includes, a) fulfilling a donation request, from credit card verification to sending you a tax receipt; b) replying to inquiries about promotions, food drives, or employment; c) following-up on volunteer inquiries; d) making changes to personal information, per individual request; e) confirming a donation request; f) to personally thank you; g) to send you additional Food Lifeline materials, by request; g) to protect the security and integrity of the site; h) to protect against a threat of safety or property damage; i) to protect against legal liability.
Regarding credit card donations, Food Lifeline works with several designated credit card companies. To fulfill these transactions, it is necessary that the third party has your correct name, business (if applicable), address, credit card number, and expiration date. The third-party entity’s firewalls and encryption technology are state-of-the-art and provide the highest levels of security to ensure the confidentiality of your transaction.
For Food Lifeline monthly donors making recurring electronic donations with a credit card or bank account, Food Lifeline works with a third party to enact automatic deductions from your credit card or bank account, per your authorization and specifications. If your information changes, it is important that you contact us at give@foodlifeline.org or via telephone at (206) 545-6600 with updates.
To reiterate, Food Lifeline will not use your personal information in any other way than what is stated in the Privacy Policy. Food Lifeline employees, agents, and contractors who have access to personal information are required to protect the data pursuant to the Privacy Policy.
How To Opt Out or Update Information
When you make a donation to Food Lifeline, you can elect to have Food Lifeline publications or other pertinent information sent to you. If you want to make any changes to the material you receive, simply email Food Lifeline at give@foodlifeline.org.  You can also write to us at 815 South 96th Street, Seattle, WA 98108 or call (206) 545-6600.
Food Lifeline’s Secure Environment
Food Lifeline protects your online donation information by using Secure Sockets Layer (“SSL”). This technology works by encrypting the information you disclose to Food Lifeline during a donation transaction to prevent anyone other than Food Lifeline from decoding your personal information.
No Liability
Security measures of any kind are not immune to any loss, misuse, or alteration of information on the site and Food Lifeline is not responsible for any damages or liabilities relating to any such security failures. By using this site, individuals understand that any information, communication (including email and other electronic communications) may be accessed by unauthorized third parties when communicated over the internet.
Food Lifeline reserves the right to change its Privacy Policy at any time. Food Lifeline will post and highlight any changes on this site.
Terms & Conditions of Use
By using, browsing, and/or accessing Food Lifeline’s website, you acknowledge that you have read, understood, and agree to be bound by these terms and conditions of use, including the Privacy Policy (collectively, the “terms”), and comply with all United States laws and regulations that are applicable. In effect, by agreeing to the terms and using Food Lifeline’s website, you understand that the agreement has the same legal force and effect as a written contract with your signature and satisfies any laws that require a signature or writing. This includes applicable statute of fraud. You also consent not to challenge the validity, enforceability, or admissibility of the terms on the grounds that it is electronically transmitted or authorized. Additionally, you acknowledge that you have the opportunity to print the terms.
Permission & Copyright
All content, data, logos, and trademarks are subject to the copyright and trademark laws of the United States and, unless otherwise noted, the property of Food Lifeline. If an individual or organization would like to use the information (text or images) for commercial use, electronic re-publication, or print publication, they must receive written permission from Food Lifeline. To get permission, please contact info@foodlifeline.org or call (206) 545-6600. If any of the information is used, Food Lifeline must be named as the original source of the information.
Links
Food Lifeline’s website may include links to other web sites that are not under Food Lifeline’s control. By linking to another site, Food Lifeline does not endorse or imply any association with a linked site. Food Lifeline is not responsible for the accuracy, legality, content, or virus-free operation of any linked site.
Warranty and Disclaimer
The content on Food Lifeline’s site, including services, information, and access are provided “as is,” without any type of warranty, expressly or implied. Food Lifeline does not guarantee the site in terms of its quality, correctness, accuracy, reliability or otherwise. Furthermore, Food Lifeline does not guarantee that the site will work uninterrupted or error-free, that defects will be corrected, or that the site or the server that makes it available are free of viruses or other harmful components, or that transmission and/or access to and from the site will not be disrupted, continuous or error-free. In no event will Food Lifeline, its staff, agents, related entities, or anyone else involved in the creation, production, or delivery of these pages, be liable for any direct, incidental, punitive, or consequential damages resulting from the use of this site [or any linked site].
Disputes
Food Lifeline’s website is operated from Food Lifeline’s offices in Washington State, USA. Any dispute relating to Food Lifeline’s website shall be governed by the laws of the state of Washington without regard to its conflict of law provisions. You agree to personal jurisdiction by and venue in the state and federal courts of King County, Washington.
Donation Disclosure
Food Lifeline greatly appreciates your generosity and trust in our organization. Food Lifeline will work to the best of its abilities to ensure that your contribution is used in the most efficient and effective way possible to feed hungry people in Western Washington. Food Lifeline is a nonprofit 501 (c) (3) organization that meets the Better Business Bureau’s Wise Giving Alliance Standards for Charitable Accountability. A copy of our most recent Annual Report may be obtained from the Secretary of State.
How to Contact Food Lifeline
If you have any questions or comments concerning this Privacy Policy, please call Food Lifeline at (206) 545-6600, or mail Food Lifeline at: 815 South 96th Street, Seattle, WA 98108.
Address
Food Lifeline Hunger Solution Center
815 S 96th St
Seattle, WA  98108
Phone number
Toll Free: 1-877-404-7543
Telephone: 206-545-6600
Privacy Policy
Financial Reports
Careers
Stay Informed Receive regular updates and information on how you can address hunger in our region.
Sign Up Today
© 2020 Food Lifeline.
Need Food?
How to Help
Volunteer
Donate Funds
Give a Gift in Tribute
Season of Giving
Host a Food Drive
Virtual Food Drive
Canned Food Drive
Advocacy - Take Action
Action Takers are Food Lifeline volunteers and supporters who agree to higher levels of advocacy action-taking. This means messaging lawmakers with each alert and agreeing to more communications from the advocacy team.
Name*
First
Last
Email*
Phone*Address*
Street Address
Address Line 2
City
AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
State
ZIP Code
"Action Taker" is a special role. It means more communication from us and being part of a group of volunteers that really wants to makes things happen.*
I'm ready to join
x
Advocacy - Stay informed
Join our "Stay Informed" advocacy list to be kept up-to-date with the most important food policy action around.
Name*
First
Last
Email*
Phone*Address*
Street Address
Address Line 2
City
AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
State
ZIP Code
In order to keep you informed, we'll send you emails about the latest happenings.*
I'm ready to join
x
Food Frenzy sign up
Company*Referred by:Address
Street Address
Address Line 2
City
State / Province / Region
ZIP / Postal Code
AfghanistanÅland IslandsAlbaniaAlgeriaAmerican SamoaAndorraAngolaAnguillaAntarcticaAntigua and BarbudaArgentinaArmeniaArubaAustraliaAustriaAzerbaijanBahamasBahrainBangladeshBarbadosBelarusBelgiumBelizeBeninBermudaBhutanBoliviaBonaire, Sint Eustatius and SabaBosnia and HerzegovinaBotswanaBouvet IslandBrazilBritish Indian Ocean TerritoryBrunei DarussalamBulgariaBurkina FasoBurundiCambodiaCameroonCanadaCape VerdeCayman IslandsCentral African RepublicChadChileChinaChristmas IslandCocos IslandsColombiaComorosCongo, Democratic Republic of theCongo, Republic of theCook IslandsCosta RicaCôte d'IvoireCroatiaCubaCuraçaoCyprusCzech RepublicDenmarkDjiboutiDominicaDominican RepublicEcuadorEgyptEl SalvadorEquatorial GuineaEritreaEstoniaEswatini (Swaziland)EthiopiaFalkland IslandsFaroe IslandsFijiFinlandFranceFrench GuianaFrench PolynesiaFrench Southern TerritoriesGabonGambiaGeorgiaGermanyGhanaGibraltarGreeceGreenlandGrenadaGuadeloupeGuamGuatemalaGuernseyGuineaGuinea-BissauGuyanaHaitiHeard and McDonald IslandsHoly SeeHondurasHong KongHungaryIcelandIndiaIndonesiaIranIraqIrelandIsle of ManIsraelItalyJamaicaJapanJerseyJordanKazakhstanKenyaKiribatiKuwaitKyrgyzstanLao People's Democratic RepublicLatviaLebanonLesothoLiberiaLibyaLiechtensteinLithuaniaLuxembourgMacauMacedoniaMadagascarMalawiMalaysiaMaldivesMaliMaltaMarshall IslandsMartiniqueMauritaniaMauritiusMayotteMexicoMicronesiaMoldovaMonacoMongoliaMontenegroMontserratMoroccoMozambiqueMyanmarNamibiaNauruNepalNetherlandsNew CaledoniaNew ZealandNicaraguaNigerNigeriaNiueNorfolk IslandNorth KoreaNorthern Mariana IslandsNorwayOmanPakistanPalauPalestine, State ofPanamaPapua New GuineaParaguayPeruPhilippinesPitcairnPolandPortugalPuerto RicoQatarRéunionRomaniaRussiaRwandaSaint BarthélemySaint HelenaSaint Kitts and NevisSaint LuciaSaint MartinSaint Pierre and MiquelonSaint Vincent and the GrenadinesSamoaSan MarinoSao Tome and PrincipeSaudi ArabiaSenegalSerbiaSeychellesSierra LeoneSingaporeSint MaartenSlovakiaSloveniaSolomon IslandsSomaliaSouth AfricaSouth GeorgiaSouth KoreaSouth SudanSpainSri LankaSudanSurinameSvalbard and Jan Mayen IslandsSwedenSwitzerlandSyriaTaiwanTajikistanTanzaniaThailandTimor-LesteTogoTokelauTongaTrinidad and TobagoTunisiaTurkeyTurkmenistanTurks and Caicos IslandsTuvaluUgandaUkraineUnited Arab EmiratesUnited KingdomUnited StatesUruguayUS Minor Outlying IslandsUzbekistanVanuatuVenezuelaVietnamVirgin Islands, BritishVirgin Islands, U.S.Wallis and FutunaWestern SaharaYemenZambiaZimbabwe
Country
Sector*AccountingDesign, Engineering, or ConstructionFinancialLawPublic Sector, LegalTechnologyOtherNumber of Employees*Your company's fundraising goalAdditional informationPlease share additional information with us:
I am coordinating Food Frenzy for the first time
I am coordinating Food Frenzy for the first time
Send me information on sponsoring Food Frenzy
Send me information on sponsoring other Food Lifeline events
I am interested in being a mentor for new companies or coordinators
I would like a Food Lifeline staff member to share about Food Lifeline at my company
I plan to organize volunteer sessions for my company
Please share with us which events you or your coworkers plan to attend:
Coordinator Volunteer Session on February 21
Kickoff Party on April 19 - www.foodfrenzy.org/kickoff
Coordinator's Lunch on June 7
Company FacebookCompany TwitterCompany InstagramCoordinator informationName*
First
Last
Job title*Email*
Phone number*
Secondary coordinator (optional)
Secondary coordinator informationName
First
Last
Email
Phone number
x
Become a Food Lifeline Partner Agency
Contact name*
City
AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
State
ZIP Code
Physical address
Same as mailing address
Street Address
Address Line 2
City
AlabamaAlaskaArizonaArkansasCaliforniaColoradoConnecticutDelawareDistrict of ColumbiaFloridaGeorgiaHawaiiIdahoIllinoisIndianaIowaKansasKentuckyLouisianaMaineMarylandMassachusettsMichiganMinnesotaMississippiMissouriMontanaNebraskaNevadaNew HampshireNew JerseyNew MexicoNew YorkNorth CarolinaNorth DakotaOhioOklahomaOregonPennsylvaniaRhode IslandSouth CarolinaSouth DakotaTennesseeTexasUtahVermontVirginiaWashingtonWest VirginiaWisconsinWyomingArmed Forces AmericasArmed Forces EuropeArmed Forces Pacific
State
ZIP Code
Information about your programPlease provide a brief description of your program*Is your program a non-profit organization with a 501(c)3 designation by the IRS?*Is a service or fee required to participate in any agency programs?*How many members are on your board of directors (or board of trustees, etc.) and how frequently do they meet?*How long has your program been in operation?*Are you aware of other emergency food programs in your area (food banks, meal programs, shelters, etc)?*If yes, which programs? If no, have you looked into this?How many people per week or month are served at your program?*What types of foods are you interested in receiving?*How is your agency funded to ensure that your programs are sustainable?*Describe any food sharing relationships your agency has with other agencies*
x
Agency feedback form
Your name*
First
Last
Email*
Subject*Contact UpdateGeneral FeedbackOrder DiscrepancyTrash ConcernWebsite IssueOtherComments*
